alltheparties.com 2002-12-09

# Allnightclubs.com's Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy for AllNightclubs.com_**

 **Allnightclubs.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.AllNightclubs.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected to verify the user's identity. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

This site contains links to other sites. **www.AllNightclubs.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Since we have special relationships, such as "Powered by" partners, business partners, cobranded sites, the information that we share is on a purely demographic basis. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@Allnightclubs.com](mailto:webmaster@Allnightclubs.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: http://www.AllNightclubs.com
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address:
  4. You can call the following telephone number: 917-674-5655

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@Allnightclubs.com](mailto:webmaster@Allnightclubs.com)
  2. visit http://www.AllNightclubs.com
  3. call the following telephone number: 917-674-5655

**Contacting the Web Site**

if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

_Samuel O. Obukwelu  
Allnightclubs.com  
PO Box 1454  
New York, NY 10027  
Sam@allnightclubs.com_
